(Spock:)Trust me, it gets old after a while.
(Spock:)You must right your wrong, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Leonard has his toy,
and he's never going to open it.
(Sheldon:)So he won't know it's broken.
And I have a toy that isn't broken.
(Sheldon:)Everybody's happy.
(Spock:)Well, I am unhappy.
l thought where you come from
they don't have emotions.
(Spock:)I come from a factory in Taiwan.
(Spock:)Now, do the right thing.
(Sheldon:)You know what you are?
Well, you're a green-blooded buzzkill.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps it's time you beam on
out of here.
(Spock:)Fine. I will just use the Transporter.
(Spock:)Oh, right, you broke it.
(Sheldon:)Very well. Cooper to Enterprise,
one to beam up.
Energize.